[
    {
        "question" : "Which is a reserved word in the Java programming language?",
        "options" : 
        [
            "method",
            "native",
            "subclass",
            "reference"
        ],        
        "answer" : "native"
    },
	{
        "question" : "Which one of the following will declare an array and initialize it with five numbers?",
        "options" : 
        [
            "Array a = new Array(5);",
            "int [] a = {23,22,21,20,19};",
            "int a [] = new int[5];",
            "int [5] array;"
        ],        
        "answer" : "int [] a = {23,22,21,20,19};"
    },
	{
        "question" : "Which is the valid declarations within an interface definition?",
        "options" : 
        [
            "public double method1();",
            "public final double method1();",
            "static void method1(double d1);",
            "protected void method1(double d1);"
        ],        
        "answer" : "public double method1();"
    },
	{
        "question" : "Which one is a valid declaration of a boolean?",
        "options" : 
        [
            "boolean b1 = 0;",
            "boolean b2 = 'false';",
            "boolean b3 = false;",
            "boolean b4 = Boolean.false();"
        ],        
        "answer" : "boolean b3 = false;"
    },
	{
        "question" : "What is the numerical range of a char?",
        "options" : 
        [
            "-128 to 127",
            "-(215) to (215) - 1",
            "0 to 32767",
            "0 to 65535"
        ],        
        "answer" : "0 to 65535"
    },
	{
        "question" : "Which is a valid declaration of a String?",
        "options" : 
        [
            "String s1 = null;",
            "String s2 = 'null';",
            "String s3 = (String) 'abc';",
            "String s4 = (String) '\ufeed';"
        ],        
        "answer" : "String s1 = null;"
    },
	{
        "question" : "What is the name of the method used to start a thread execution?",
        "options" : 
        [
            "init();",
            "start();",
            "run();",
            "resume();"
        ],        
        "answer" : "start();"
    },
	{
        "question" : "Which will contain the body of the thread?",
        "options" : 
        [
            "run();",
            "start();",
            "stop();",
            "main();"
        ],        
        "answer" : "run();"
    },
	{
        "question" : "You need to store elements in a collection that guarantees that no duplicates are stored and all elements can be accessed in natural order. Which interface provides that capability?",
        "options" : 
        [
            "java.util.Map",
            "java.util.Set",
            "java.util.List",
            "java.util.Collection"
        ],        
        "answer" : "java.util.Set"
    },
	{
        "question" : "Can try statements be nested?",
        "options" : 
        [
            "Yes",
            "No"
        ],        
        "answer" : "Yes"
    }
]